Guide to the Murray Webb Latimer papers, 1930-1980 MS2082
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Papers, 1930-1980; MS2082 Series 1; 39.5 Linear feet
  - AMALGAMATED LITHOGRAPHERS OF AMERICA: -Local 1, 20% Sample, undated (Box 25, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L467.e
  - AMALGAMATED LITHOGRAPHERS OF AMERICA: -Local 1, Preliminary Report, Pension Plan- Prepared by A.G. Silverman, undated (Box 25, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system: L467.f
  - AMALGAMATED LITHOGRAPHERS OF AMERICA: -Local 1, Preliminary Report, Unemployment Insurance Plan-prepared by A.G. Silverman, undated (Box 25, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L467.g
  - AMALGAMATED LITHOGRAPHERS OF AMERICA: -Local 1, Valuation-Service Tables, Commutation Functions, Per Capita, 1949 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system: L467.1h
  - AMALGAMATED LITHOGRAPHERS OF AMERICA: -Local 1, Valuation,Report on Status of Pension Fund, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system: L467.1i
  - AMALGAMATED LITHOGRAPHERS OF AMERICA: -San Francisco Local, undated (Box 25, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L467.2
  - AMALGAMATED LITHOGRAPHERS OF AMERICA: -Inter-local Pension Fund, undated (Box 25, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system:L467.3
  - AMALGAMATED LITHOGRAPHERS OF AMERICA: -Inter-local Pension Fund, Valuation, 1952 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system:L467.3a
  - AMALGAMATED LITHOGRAPHERS OF AMERICA: -International Mortuary Fund, undated (Box 25, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system:L467.4a
  - AMALGAMATED LITHOGRAPHERS OF AMERICA: -International Mortuary Fund, Calculations, undated (Box 25, Folder 12)
    Original numbering system:L467.4b
  - AMALGAMATED LITHOGRAPHERS OF AMERICA: -Service Table with Kaiser-Fraser Retirement Rates, undated (Box 25, Folder 13)
    Original numbering system:L467.5
  - AMALGAMATED LITHOGRAPHERS OF AMERICA: -Service Tables, undated (Box 25, Folder 14)
    Original numbering system:L467.6
  - Papers, undated (Box 26)
  - AMALGAMATED LITHOGRAPHERS OF AMERICA: -Local 1 Valuation(book), 1947 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L467.7
  - AMALGAMATED LITHOGRAPHERS OF AMERICA: -Work for Basic Salary Scale Based on Amal. Lithographers and Telephone Workers(book), 1950 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L467.8
  - AMALGAMATED LITHOGRAPHERS OF AMERICA: Local 1, Valuation:Exposures,Contributions ,Numbers of Members,Comparisons,Book 1: Book 2,2 1/4 % Service Table Commutation Functions, Summaries:Book 3, 2 1/2 % Commutation Functions, undated (Box 26, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L467.9
  - AMALGAMATED LITHOGRAPHERS OF AMERICA: -Per Capita,Lithographers with Kaiser Fraser Retirement Rates, undated (Box 26, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L467.11
  - Papers, undated (Box 27)
  - UNITED MINE WORKERS OF AMERICA: -Correspondence, undated (Box 27, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L468
  - UNITED MINE WORKERS OF AMERICA: -Calculations, undated (Box 27, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L468.1
  - UNITED MINE WORKERS OF AMERICA: Miscl., undated (Box 27, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L468.2
  - UNITED MINE WORKERS OF AMERICA: -Towers,Perrin.Foster, & Crosby, Inc. Report to Bituminous Coal Operators on Welfare and Retirement Benefits for Employees, Includes M.W.L. Comments, undated (Box 27, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L468.3
  - UNITED MINE WORKERS OF AMERICA: -Robert T. Myers, "Further Experiences of U.M.W.A. Welfare and Retirement Plan ", 1961 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L468.4
  - UNITED MINE WORKERS OF AMERICA: -1974 Pension Trust.1950 Pension and Benefit Plans and Trust, 1950-1974 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L468.6
  - WAR AGENCIES EMPLOYEES PROTECTIVE ASSOCIATION: -Miscl, undated (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:L469
  - WAR AGENCIES EMPLOYEES PROTECTIVE ASSOCIATION: -Continuation of Accidental Death and Dismemberment Benefits, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L469.1
  - UNITED AUTOMOBILE WORKERS: -General Correspondence, undated (Box 27, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system:L470
  - UNITED AUTOMOBILE WORKERS: -General Correspondence, undated (Box 27, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system:L470.1
  - UNITED AUTOMOBILE WORKERS: -Social Security Program, undated (Box 27, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system:L470.1a
  - UNITED AUTOMOBILE WORKERS: -Miscl. Publications, undated (Box 27, Folder 12)
    Original numbering system:L470.1b
  - Papers, undated (Box 28)
  - UNITED AUTOMOBILE WORKERS: -Supplemental Unemployment Benefits, undated (Box 28, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L470.1c
  - UNITED AUTOMOBILE WORKERS: -Ford-U.A.W. Pension Plan, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L470.2
  - UNITED AUTOMOBILE WORKERS: - Settlement, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L470.3a
  - UNITED AUTOMOBILE WORKERS: -Ford Moter Co., undated (Box 28, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L470.3b
  - UNITED AUTOMOBILE WORKERS: -Ford.Moter Co.,Supplemental UnemploymentBenefit Plan, undated (Box 28, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L470.3c
  - UNITED AUTOMOBILE WORKERS: -Ford-Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L470.4a
  - UNITED AUTOMOBILE WORKERS: -General Moters Corporation, undated (Box 28, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:L470.4b
  - UNITED AUTOMOBILE WORKERS: -Chrysler Corporation, undated (Box 28, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L470.5a
  - UNITED AUTOMOBILE WORKERS: -Ford Insurance Programs, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system:L470.5b
  - UNITED AUTOMOBILE WORKERS: -Settlements, Genl. Moters, Ford, Chrysler, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system: L470.6
  - UNITED AUTOMOBILE WORKERS: -General Motors Hourly Rated Employee Pension Plan. Also Chrysler, Teledyne Continental Moter, undated (Box 28, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system: L470.7
  - UNITED AUTOMOBILE WORKERS: -,Miscl., 1976 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    Original numbering system:L470.8
  - GEORGE TRANSFER AND RIGGING COMPANY: -Insurance, undated (Box 28, Folder 13)
    Original numbering system:L471.a
  - GEORGE TRANSFER AND RIGGING COMPANY: -Insurance, undated (Box 28, Folder 14)
    Original numbering system:L471.b
  - GEORGE TRANSFER AND RIGGING COMPANY: -Correspondence, Comparison of Proposals, undated (Box 28, Folder 15)
    Original numbering system: L471.c
  - Papers, undated (Box 29)
  - NEIMAN MARCUS: -Correspondence, undated (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system: L471.la
  - NEIMAN MARCUS: -Salary Scale and Censuses, undated (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L471.lb
  - NEIMAN MARCUS: -Pension Commputations, undated (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L471.2
  - NEIMAN MARCUS: Republic of Germany, Dr. Diether H. Hoffman of Bank Fur Gemeinwirtschaft-BFG Reports, undated (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L472.a
  - SCHENLEY INDUSTRIES INC.: -Insurance Plan, Correspondence, undated (Box 29, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L472.1av
  - SCHENLEY INDUSTRIES INC.: -Insurance Plan, Rates, Census,Act, undated (Box 29, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L472.1b
  - SCHENLEY INDUSTRIES INC.: -Insurance Plan, undated (Box 29, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:L472.2
  - SCHENLEY INDUSTRIES INC.: -Insurance Plan, Dirivation of Numerators-Misc. Worksheets, undated (Box 29, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L472.3
  - SCHENLEY INDUSTRIES INC.: -Insurance Plan, Calculations, undated (Box 29, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system: L472.4
  - SCHENLEY INDUSTRIES INC.: -Ins. Plan, Per Capitas and Final Summaries, undated (Box 29, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system:L472.5
  - SCHENLEY INDUSTRIES INC.: -Pension Plan, Correspondence, undated (Box 29, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system:L473
  - SCHENLEY INDUSTRIES INC.: -Pension Valuations, Male/Female, undated (Box 29, Folder 12)
    Original numbering system: L473.1
  - Papers, undated (Box 30)
  - COMMERCIAL TELEGRAPHERS: -United Press Division, undated (Box 30, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L474.1
  - COMMERCIAL TELEGRAPHERS: -Western Union Division, undated (Box 30, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L474.2
  - COMMERCIAL TELEGRAPHERS: -Western Union Division Service Table, Female,2 1/2%, undated (Box 30, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system: L474.2a
  - COMMERCIAL TELEGRAPHERS: -Western Union Division Service Tables, Male, 2 1/2 7, undated (Box 30, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L474.2b
  - COMMERCIAL TELEGRAPHERS: -Western Union Division Western Union Mortality & Commutation Colunms, undated (Box 30, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L474.3
  - FREEPORT SULPHUR COMPANY: -General, undated (Box 30, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system: L475
  - FREEPORT SULPHUR COMPANY: -Service Tables, undated (Box 30, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system: L475.1
  - FREEPORT SULPHUR COMPANY: -Company Records of Employee Service, undated (Box 30, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L475.2
  - FREEPORT SULPHUR COMPANY: --Statistical Tabulations of Service Records, undated (Box 30, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system:L475.3
  - FREEPORT SULPHUR COMPANY: -Data on People Over 55 in 1948 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system:L475.4
  - FREEPORT SULPHUR COMPANY: -Actual Cost Of Insurance Over $3000, undated (Box 30, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system:L475.5
  - FREEPORT SULPHUR COMPANY: -Calculations Started (Incomplete), 1949 October (Box 30, Folder 12)
    Original numbering system:L475.6
  - FREEPORT SULPHUR COMPANY: -Unfinished Material, undated (Box 30, Folder 13)
    Original numbering system:L475.6a
  - MILK AND ICE CREAM SALESMEN DRIVERS AND DAIRY EMPLOYEES: -Pension Plan, undated (Box 30, Folder 14)
    Original numbering system:L476
  - MILK AND ICE CREAM SALESMEN DRIVERS AND DAIRY EMPLOYEES: -Calculations, undated (Box 30, Folder 15)
    Original numbering system:L476.1
  - MILK AND ICE CREAM SALESMEN DRIVERS AND DAIRY EMPLOYEES: Federal Bar Association,Accident and Sickness Insurance, undated (Box 30, Folder 16)
    Original numbering system:L477
  - Papers, undated (Box 31)
  - UNITED STEEL WORKERS OF AMERICA: -Miscl Documents, undated (Box 31, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L478.3
  - UNITED STEEL WORKERS OF AMERICA: -Chrysler Corp.,Youngstown, Ohio, Supplemental Benefit Termination, 1958 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L478.4
  - UNITED STEEL WORKERS OF AMERICA: -Analysis of Three Major Companies-Insurance Reports, 1951-1953 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L478.5
  - UNITED STEEL WORKERS OF AMERICA: -Insurance and Pension Reports, undated (Box 31, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L478.6
  - UNITED STEEL WORKERS OF AMERICA: -Review of Steel Experience-General, undated (Box 31, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L478.7
  - UNITED STEEL WORKERS OF AMERICA: - Questionaire, Insurance Analysis Forms, 1953 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L478.8
  - UNITED STEEL WORKERS OF AMERICA: -Questionaire Study,General, 1953-1954 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:L478.9
  - UNITED STEEL WORKERS OF AMERICA: -General Outline of Insurance and pension Study, 1953 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L478.11a
  - UNITED STEEL WORKERS OF AMERICA: -Study Forms, 1951-1953 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system:L478.11b
  - UNITED STEEL WORKERS OF AMERICA: -Questionaires, Pensions, 1953 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system:L478.12
  - UNITED STEEL WORKERS OF AMERICA: -Insurance and Pensions Study Committee, 1953 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system:L478.13
  - UNITED STEEL WORKERS OF AMERICA: -Steel Pension Study, 1954 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    Original numbering system:L478.14a
  - UNITED STEEL WORKERS OF AMERICA: - Study-Draft Forms, 1953 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    Original numbering system:L478.14b
  - UNITED STEEL WORKERS OF AMERICA: -Bluecross Memo Concerning Steel Workers, undated (Box 31, Folder 14)
    Original numbering system:L478.15
  - UNITED STEEL WORKERS OF AMERICA: -Insurance and Pension Reports, undated (Box 31, Folder 15)
    Original numbering system:L478.16
  - UNITED STEEL WORKERS OF AMERICA: -U.S. Steel Experience-Joint Study of Pensions and Insurance-United States Steel Corporation & United Steelworkers, 1953 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    Original numbering system:L478.17
  - UNITED STEEL WORKERS OF AMERICA: -Bethlehem Steel, Joint Study Of Pensions and Insurance, 1953 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    Original numbering system: L478.18
  - UNITED STEEL WORKERS OF AMERICA: -Bethlehem Joint Study-Bethlehem Data, undated (Box 31, Folder 18)
    Original numbering system:L478.19
  - UNITED STEEL WORKERS OF AMERICA: -Joint Study, Bethlehem Pension Tabulations Instructions, undated (Box 31, Folder 19)
    Original numbering system:L478.21
  - UNITED STEEL WORKERS OF AMERICA: -Form Letters Concerning Ins., Pensions,and Supplemental Unemployment Benefits, 1960 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    Original numbering system: L478.22
  - UNITED STEEL WORKERS OF AMERICA: - Survey, Follow up Letters, 1960 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    Original numbering system:L478.23
  - UNITED STEEL WORKERS OF AMERICA: - Survey, Pittsburgh, 1960 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    Original numbering system:L478.24
  - UNITED STEEL WORKERS OF AMERICA: - Latimer Report, Chapts 1, Tables, 1960 (Box 31, Folder 23)
    Original numbering system:L478.25a
  - UNITED STEEL WORKERS OF AMERICA: - Latimer Report, chapt 2, 1960 (Box 31, Folder 24)
    Original numbering system:L478.25b
  - UNITED STEEL WORKERS OF AMERICA: -Special Report on Insurance, Pensions, and Supplemental Unemployment Benefits of 10th Constitutional Convention, Report, undated (Box 31, Folder 25)
    Original numbering system:L478.26
  - UNITED STEEL WORKERS OF AMERICA: -, 10th Constitutional Convention, Report, 1960 (Box 31, Folder 26)
    Original numbering system:L478.26a
  - UNITED STEEL WORKERS OF AMERICA: -, 10th ConstitutionalConvention, Special Report-Press Release, 1960 (Box 31, Folder 27)
    Original numbering system:L478.26b
  - UNITED STEEL WORKERS OF AMERICA: -, 10th Const. Convention, Officers Report, 1960 (Box 31, Folder 28)
    Original numbering system:L478 26c
  - UNITED STEEL WORKERS OF AMERICA: -1962 Negotiations, 11 Companies, Census as of1962, 1962 December 31 (Box 31, Folder 29)
    Original numbering system:L478.27D
  - UNITED STEEL WORKERS OF AMERICA: -Service Tables, undated (Box 31, Folder 30)
    Original numbering system: L478.28
  - Papers, undated (Box 32)
  - Consultants, undated (Box 32, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L479
  - Railroad Retirement-Other Railroads, undated (Box 32, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L479.11B
  - SAN FRANSISCO OAKLAND NEWSPAPER GUILD (SFONG) AND SAN FRANSISCO NEWSPAPER PUBLISHERS ASSOCIATION (SFNPA): -Misc., 1955 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L486
  - SAN FRANSISCO OAKLAND NEWSPAPER GUILD (SFONG) AND SAN FRANSISCO NEWSPAPER PUBLISHERS ASSOCIATION (SFNPA): -Retirement Income Plan, 1955-1957 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L486.1
  - SAN FRANSISCO OAKLAND NEWSPAPER GUILD (SFONG) AND SAN FRANSISCO NEWSPAPER PUBLISHERS ASSOCIATION (SFNPA): Retirement-Income Plan, Calculations, 1955 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L486.1A
  - SFONG AND SFNPA: - Retirement Income Plan, 1958 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L486.1B
  - SFONG AND SFNPA: - Retirement Income Plan, 1959-1960 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:L486.1C
  - SFONG AND SFNPA: - Retirement Income Plane, 1965-1968 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L486.1D
  - SFONG AND SFNPA: -San Francisco and San Mateo Times Pension Program -SFONG, undated (Box 32, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system:L486.2
  - SFONG AND SFNPA: -Santa Rosa Press Democrat Pension Program SFONG, undated (Box 32, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system:L486.3
  - SFONG AND SFNPA: -Oakland Tribune,Inclusion in SFONG Pension Program, undated (Box 32, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system:L486.4
  - SFONG AND SFNPA: -SFONG Retirement Income Plan,San Fran.-Oakland and Stockton Guilds and Six Papers 1.East Bay Labor Journel 2.Vallejo News Chronicle 3.Vallejo Times-Herald 4.Santa Rosa Press Chronicle 5.Independent 6.Naps Register, undated (Box 32, Folder 12)
    Original numbering system:L486.5
  - Papers, undated (Box 33)
  - SFONG AND SFNPA: -SFONG,San fran. and Stockton and 6 Papers(the above) Retirement Income Plan, undated (Box 33, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L486.5A
  - SFONG AND SFNPA: -SFONG Olympic Press,San Fran. and Stockton Guilds-Retirement Income Plans, undated (Box 33, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L486.5B
  - SFONG AND SFNPA: -SFONG-gtockton Record Pension Plan, undated (Box 33, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L486.5C
  - SFONG AND SFNPA: SFONG-SFNPA-Retire. Income Plan- Liberalization of "1 (a) Benefits, 1961 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L486.6
  - SFONG AND SFNPA: -SFONG, City- Wide Health and Welfare, undated (Box 33, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L486.7
  - AMERICAN NEWSPAPER GUILD: -Members Retirement Income Plan, undated (Box 33, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L488A
  - AMERICAN NEWSPAPER GUILD:, 1947-1960 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:L488.1
  - AMERICAN NEWSPAPER GUILD:, 1954-1957 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L488.1a
  - AMERICAN NEWSPAPER GUILD: -Calcualtions, 1948 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system:L488.2
  - AMERICAN NEWSPAPER GUILD: -Calculations, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system:L488.2c
  - AMERICAN NEWSPAPER GUILD: -Pension Plan, Report, 1948 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system:L488.3
  - AMERICAN NEWSPAPER GUILD: -Associated Press, undated (Box 33, Folder 12)
    Original numbering system:L488.4
  - AMERICAN NEWSPAPER GUILD: -Times, Inc., undated (Box 33, Folder 13)
    Original numbering system:L488.5
  - AMERICAN NEWSPAPER GUILD: -New York Post, undated (Box 33, Folder 14)
    Original numbering system:L488.6
  - AMERICAN NEWSPAPER GUILD: -Amphlet Printing Co., undated (Box 33, Folder 15)
    Original numbering system:L488.7
  - KAISER FRAZER CORPORATION: -Social Security Fund, 1948 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    Original numbering system:L489.1x
  - KAISER FRAZER CORPORATION: -Social Security Fund, 1949 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    Original numbering system:L489.1a
  - KAISER FRAZER CORPORATION: -Social Security Fund, 1950-1952 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    Original numbering system:L489.1b
  - Papers, undated (Box 34)
  - KAISER FRAZER CORPORATION: -Social Security Fund-Financial Status of SS Fund, 1952 May 05 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L489.1c
  - KAISER FRAZER CORPORATION: -Misc. Tables, undated (Box 34, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L489.2
  - KAISER FRAZER CORPORATION: -Agreement and Declaration of Trust, undated (Box 34, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L489.3
  - KAISER FRAZER CORPORATION: -Retirement Trust Agreement, undated (Box 34, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L489.3a
  - KAISER FRAZER CORPORATION: -Investment Agreement, undated (Box 34, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L489.3b
  - KAISER FRAZER CORPORATION: -Pension Calculations, 1950 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L489.4
  - KAISER FRAZER CORPORATION: -Pension Calculations, 2951, Optional Retirements Age 60, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:L489.4a
  - KAISER FRAZER CORPORATION: -Service Records, 1949-1950 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L489.5
  - KAISER FRAZER CORPORATION: -Service Records, 1950 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system:L489.5a
  - KAISER FRAZER CORPORATION: -Censuses as of 1950, 1950 August 31 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system:L489.6
  - KAISER FRAZER CORPORATION: -Per Capita Sheets,male/female at 2 1/4%, undated (Box 34, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system:L489.6a
  - KAISER FRAZER CORPORATION: -Retirement Trust Fund,-Correspondence, 1949-1950 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    Original numbering system:L489.7
  - KAISER FRAZER CORPORATION: -Retierment Trust Fund -Correspondence, 1951-1953 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    Original numbering system:L489.7A
  - KAISER FRAZER CORPORATION: -Retirement Trust Fund -Submission to Internal Revenue, 1951 June (Box 34, Folder 14)
    Original numbering system:L489.7B
  - Papers, undated (Box 35)
  - KAISER FRAZER CORPORATION: -Retirement Trust Fund -Correspondence, 1954-1956 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L489.7C
  - KAISER FRAZER CORPORATION: -Retirement Trust Fund -Correspondence, 1957-1959 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L489.7D
  - KAISER FRAZER CORPORATION: -Retirement Trust Fund -Correspondence, 1960 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L489.7E
  - KAISER FRAZER CORPORATION: -Retirement Trust Fund -Valuation as of 06/30/1952, 1952 June 30 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L489.8
  - KAISER FRAZER CORPORATION: -Retirement Trust Fund -Insurance Company Bids on Annuities, 1954 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L489.9
  - KAISER FRAZER CORPORATION: -Retirement Trust Fund -Ins. Co. Bids on Annuities, 1956 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L489.9A
  - KAISER FRAZER CORPORATION: -Retirement Trust Fund - Valuation, Dissolution, Willow Run and Jackson Plants; Insurance Values, 1953 June 30 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:L489.10
  - KAISER FRAZER CORPORATION: -Retirement Trust Fund - Valuation, Insurance Values, Pension Credits, All Plants, 1953 June 30 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system: L489.10A
  - KAISER FRAZER CORPORATION: -Retirement Trust Fund - Val.,Per Caps.,Commutation Colunms, Census Multiplications, Normals, Death Benefits, Miscl., 1953 June 30 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system: L489.10B
  - KAISER FRAZER CORPORATION: -Retirement Trust Fund - Val., Census Tabulations, 1953 June 30 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system:L489.1OC
  - KAISER FRAZER CORPORATION: -Retirement Trust Fund - Val.,Census Tabulations, 1954 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system:L489.11
  - KAISER FRAZER CORPORATION: -Retirement Trust Fund - Valuation, Operating Plants, Census,Tabulation, 1954 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    Original numbering system: L489.11A
  - KAISER FRAZER CORPORATION: -Retirement Trust Fund -- Val.,Insurance Values of Pension Credits, 1954 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    Original numbering system:L489.11B
  - KAISER FRAZER CORPORATION: -Retirement Trust Fund - Val.,Shady Side, 1955 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    Original numbering system:L489.12
  - KAISER FRAZER CORPORATION: -Retirement Trust Fund - Val., 1955 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    Original numbering system:L489.12A
  - KAISER FRAZER CORPORATION: -Retirement Trust Fund -Val. and Projection Based on Census, 1956 July 01 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    Original numbering system:L489.13
  - KAISER FRAZER CORPORATION: -Retirement Trust Fund - Val.-General, 1960 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    Original numbering system:L489.14
  - Papers, undated (Box 36)
  - KAISER FRAZER CORPORATION: -Retirement Trust Fund - Calculations, 1960 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L489.14a
  - KAISER FRAZER CORPORATION: -Retirement Trust Fund -Printed Material, undated (Box 36, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L489.15
  - KAISER FRAZER CORPORATION: -Retirement Trust Fund -Val. as of 10/01/1962, 1962 October 01 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L489.16
  - KAISER FRAZER CORPORATION: -Retirement Trust Fund -Val. as of 10/01/1962 Calculations, 1962 October 01 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L489.16A